the code that we have is a liability and
the system is the asset that we're
building. Phoenix architecture takes the
same exact idea, but it says ideally
what you should have is some sort of a
specification for the system and then
the code you should think about is just
an implementation detail or a build
artifact. And the reason it's called
Phoenix architecture is like the
metaphor of the Phoenix that's destroyed
and rebuilt and you know, rises from the
ashes.
But the entire architecture is about
constantly replacing every piece of the
system, but not replacing the system as
a whole. The goal here is to be able to
deploy code in production that was
generated by AI of some sort that humans
never reviewed. We know that's what's
going to happen because we know human
behavior and it's way too easy to do
that now. So there people are always
going to do the easy thing. So let's
figure out systems that make the easy
thing okay to do. You have a statement
that said evaluations are the real code
base. How do you think about durability?
What is it that as I build a key or as I
build up anything persists across?
That's a good question.
>> [music]
>> Back in November, we hosted the first
ever in-person AI Native DevCon in New
York. This June 1st and 2nd, [music]
we're bringing it to London. It's two
days built for AI Native developers and
engineering [music] teams. One day full
of hands-on workshops and one day full
of practical talks on agent skills,
contact engineering, agent
orchestration, and enablement platforms
[music] and how teams are actually
shipping AI in production.
Join us at the brewery in London near
the Barbican for all of that plus
networking, parties, giveaways, and a
room full of people building the future
of AI Native development. You can also
join us from anywhere in the world via
the live stream.
As you're listening to this podcast, you
get 30% off your ticket with code pod30.
Just head to ainativedevcon.io
and we'll see you in London.
Hello everyone. Thanks for tuning back
into the AI Native Dev. Uh today we are
going to go uh I don't know if it's far
into the future, but definitely looking
into the future or the concepts of it uh
with Chad Fowler who is a VC today, but
don't hold it against him. You know,
he's a today at Blue Yard Capital
uh but uh he really has this sort of
rich technical background on it. You
know, some of you might know him as as
the the person leading Ruby Central uh
at the time when Ruby was all the rage
it feels like uh
feels like a while ago. Uh
>> [laughter]
>> but then
innovative, you know, I think you were
CTO at
uh Wunderkind. Not sure how to even call
that, which is sold to Microsoft uh and
you were CTO for a variety of of
departments and sort of areas for
Microsoft then uh and generally I think
a fairly well-known uh thought leader in
the space. Um and specifically, you
know, for for this podcast, what pulled
you in is that you've been writing some
really interesting blog posts and like
little storylines and perspectives on
the future of software development and
where that is headed in the Phoenix
architecture blog, which is
inconveniently posted on
aicoding.leaflet.pub.
Every time I have to like find that. Uh
but it's really really good uh blog,
really really good ideas, which we will
talk about today. Uh so Chad, thanks for
coming onto the show here and sharing
some perspectives. Yeah, thanks for
having me. Um it's
a totally exciting time to be talking
about software development. So I want to
do as much of it as as I can.
Yeah, yeah. I'm fully fully agree with
it. Like and suddenly interesting,
cerebral, fast-moving uh
a lot of this excitement and never
boring. Super interesting.
>> Yeah.
So I guess before we So we're going to
talk a lot about the Phoenix
architecture and I want to maybe like
dedicate some specific focus on on what
you mean by this.
Uh but maybe for starters, I know you
there was a bit of a like a origin for
all of these things thinking and you
were you were sort of thinking about
code is disposable and and these types
of
uh views for a while now. So can I for
starters just have you tell us a little
bit the origin story of How did you come
to this line of thinking and
um how how that came about?
>> Yeah, I guess you know, it started with
um
in the the early 2000s, somehow I ended
up in this line of consulting and
full-time jobs where my my job was to
euthanize an existing software system.
So come find some system that's like
doing good work, but can't keep up with
the demands like the technical demands
or the the business demands um
uh posed to it.
And so I'd come along and kill the
systems and I started getting really
tired of that because I was thinking
about like what about my own systems
that I create? Like think about how much
time and effort and emotion I put into
my work.
How can we build systems that can
outlive us? Like why why are we building
all these systems that are dying within
like five years? It's insane. And so I
started thinking a lot about legacy and
what that word means and also just like
biological biological metaphors for
software development because I thought,
well, I don't take very great care of
myself as a human, but I'm still here.
How is that possible? You know, we take
we spend all this money on software
systems and they still sort of get
corrupted and die
you know, fail under their own weight.
And so uh
a couple of sort of key insights came to
me. One of which I didn't really act on
much over the years. The first one is
just about infrastructure and I started
thinking about, you know, how we in the
like '90s, we'd be excited about uptime
for a given server. You know, we install
these massive big Sun servers or
whatever and I remember one that had
been up for like two years without being
rebooted. Terrifying, but back then we
were we were proud of it. Yeah. And I
realized that like if you want to be
able to change things, you need to do it
all the time. And so, you know, this
sort of behavior, whether it be an
infrastructure or software, would lead
to situations where you just couldn't
progress the system because you're not
practicing change. So the first insight
that I had in this sort of legacy thing
is let's just kill things over and over
and over so that we can be used to
killing. And I started with
infrastructure.
And now it's just like old hat, the idea
of immutable infrastructure, but like
never ever modify a server, always
replace it. Which of course you couldn't
do with physical hardware, but you can
do with containers and you know, EC2
instances is what we were doing back
then. Right. But not not just even for
the purpose of
uh of kind of learning and the agility,
but also to to know that you can do it,
to really truly know that you're able to
recover from a server failure is to do
it all the time intentionally.
>> Right. Right. And why is that? Why like
why is that the rule? It's because if
you cannot change the system, it means
you don't actually understand the
system. Mhm. So, you know, if you're
changing it constantly, you understand
what the requirements are. Just you have
to, right? So the same should be true in
software, but it was much more
expensive, you know, 15 years ago or so
to just throw away code all the time.
But I was thinking a lot about like what
would it mean to have
uh disposable software, immutable code.
So as soon as you write like one unit of
work, whatever that is, you never modify
it again, you just throw it away
uh because the unit of code itself is
small enough
uh and like bounded enough that you can
understand what it's supposed to do
trivially and therefore you can safely
replace it. So this is the sort of
backstory
that when when you pit it against where
we are in terms of like LLM generated
code, it starts to click and you say, oh
okay. Uh and we can go into that in more
detail later, but that's sort of the the
origin story of this thinking. So I I I
love that and I love the the analogy to
immutable infrastructure because I think
so many DevOps analogies are helpful, at
least to me or to people that have kind
of been through the DevOps change to to
be able to to kind of apply those to AI
and try and forecast where it's headed.
You know, the fact that servers are
statistical creatures, right? And they
you know, they don't always behave the
way we want them and so we we need to
deal with a world in which it's not
deterministic and to and to move those.
So I love the software to or rather
immutable infrastructure concept and
applying that to immutable software uh
and think, okay, what what have we
learned about immutable infrastructure
that we need to now kind of represent
here? Right. Yeah, there's also like as
you were talking, I was thinking there's
also this thing back in the day like
when I talked about how proud I was of
my two-year uptime on a server,
I also knew that server's name and I
knew its IP address and I like set it up
myself physically. I cared about it. You
know what I mean? Yeah. So I was like
attached to this thing.
And when you get to immutable
infrastructure, you can never be
attached to like one running instance of
your your software stack. I I think the
same sort of lesson applies to code,
too. Yeah. We have all developed,
especially developers, this
almost fetish-like uh
worship of our code, forgetting that the
code is not actually the thing we're
trying to build. It's just the
implementation of the thing we're trying
to build. Yeah. Yeah, no, I I love that.
That's you know, in in DevOps there's a
whole ethos of cattle versus pets,
right? You have the the ones that you're
nurturing as pets, uh which is what
you're describing and it's it's um
it is a really interesting thought to
say how do you think of code as cattle
uh and you know, you you just have
plenty of it and you keep swapping it,
which was just not feasible before. Just
like
immutable infrastructure was not really
feasible or practical, I guess, except
for very unique circumstances uh before
the cloud enabled it. Yeah. So I mean,
how would you how would you make it
feasible? Um
even back then, you know, as I said I
was like starting to think about this,
the first rule when when I was working
on Wunderlist was you can do code code
in any language you want as long as it's
no more than this big.
And so, you know, I'd literally say
this. So it just means
>> trying for a small amount. Just between
like
>> Yeah. Roughly roughly like it fits on a
page of your editor. So if you have
really good eyes, you can have a you
know, You know, have more code cuz the
font can be smaller.
But we actually did this and we did this
sort of like radical microservices
architecture.
And there were at least a couple of
cases where code was disposable because
of this.
Um we had like
uh consistent calling conventions and
sort of just, you know, we had like a
way of dealing with mutations offline
and we had a way of dealing with REST
and CRUD sort of stuff through the the
system. And it was all consistent. Um
And all the code was tiny. Which meant
we were able to replace things. So the
two versions of this, one I had written
a service in Haskell. Uh and I was one
of only two people who would tolerate
even looking at Haskell. I loved it.
>> Write-only code.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, well, yeah. In fact, in this case
that was the problem. So
the
we had to change this code so
infrequently that it became the build
system became stale underneath it.
And after we were acquired, we could not
recompile the code anymore. It still
worked. It was great. But the like
toolchain had broken underneath us cuz
we didn't have that rigor of constantly
changing it. So there was a problem with
it at one point and someone just said,
well, we're just going to rewrite this
in Go or something. So they rewrote it
rewrote it in like an afternoon and
deployed it. It was fine, you know.
Yeah. And the other thing was we we had
deployed
a major release of Wunderlist, which was
like the, you know, sort of crown
achievement of what we did technically.
And when we did it, we had
literally hundreds of server instances
running these heavy Ruby on Rails
servers.
Because that's what we knew. It was like
a consistent choice. But then afterward,
over the course of like 3 months, we
replaced something like 70% of the code
base.
Uh with Clojure, Go, Rust, etc. And made
it, like, I don't know. I think it cost
like 25% of what it did at launch to to
run because we were able to replace all
these systems that were running Ruby.
Because they were all just tiny little
things with consistent calling
conventions and easy to plug in.
That was our first attempt at doing this
sort of disposable code thing. No, no, I
love that. And I think
some of the kind of clear modularity
goes all the way back to sort of Java
design partner design patterns. You
know, just thinking about,
you know, abstracting of factories of
factories and
kind of creation of those that at least
from a dynamism of the software and the
ability to hot load different components
will come in. And I guess we still think
of the code itself often times as the
thing that is precious even if we
modularized it within the system. And I
guess, you know, this is a AI land or AI
era now. And so clearly that is now
changing. So maybe tell us a little bit
about the the the Phoenix architecture.
I I I love in general a lot of the
storytelling you have on the blog. But,
you know, some of these
visual analogies are are helpful and and
fun. So you talk about Phoenix
architecture, you talk about
regenerative software. So what's the I
mean you've you've already alluded to
some of it. But tell us a bit about
what's the philosophy behind that. Sure,
yeah. So, you know, if you think about
what I was just saying about consistent
calling conventions and and generally
conventions for like what the interfaces
would be, you know, how you think about
uh CRUD operations on data. And you
know, this doesn't just apply, of
course, to CRUD-based REST apps. But um
these are all ways of constraining a
system so that you understand how the
components interact with each other so
that the components could then be
uh potentially implemented in any
language or, you know, framework or
whatever. You still have the idea of how
the system works. And one thing I used
to always say to the team at Wunderlist
is
the code that we have is a liability and
the system is the asset that we're
building.
Uh and the Phoenix architecture takes
this and sort of codifies it. And I also
have a not yet released, but eventually
open source project called Phoenix,
which is like the actual implementation
of all this stuff I'm talking about. Um
It codifies it and it says
uh any software in the system you should
think about like it's a
build artifact. So, you know, imagine
you have a makefile or ant file or
whatever the dependency-oriented build
system thing as you know.
There's always some um sort of top-level
asset that you start with. Usually it's
code in a high-level language. And you
run a thing and it know it understands
the path and it can compile all the way
through. It can invalidate any object
code that's changed. You know, if you're
talking about like a truly compiled
system or a VM type system like JVM.
Uh and it can replace just the paths
that need to be changed. But the
top-level like asset that you're
building in that case is the Java code
or the C code or the Rust code.
The Phoenix architecture takes the same
exact idea.
But it says ideally what you should have
is some sort of a specification for the
system.
And then the code you should think about
as just an implementation detail or a
build artifact.
And the reason it's called Phoenix
architecture is that, you know, you
these like the metaphor of the Phoenix
that's destroyed and rebuilt and, you
know, rises from the ashes.
But the entire architecture is about
constantly replacing every piece of the
system, but not replacing the system as
a whole. Because you need that sort of
consistent shape and calling convention
for for interacting with the system
you know, generatively.
And so um
yeah, that's sort of the key thing of
if
if we want to be able to change systems
safely and rapidly and we want that to
be how we interact with our systems.
They're just like very change um
friendly.
Then
like I take a lesson actually from
extreme programming, Kent Beck, all
those people in the early Agile days. If
something's hard, just do it all all the
time. So if testing is hard, then do it
all the time. If code review is hard or
expensive, then just do it all the time
by doing pair programming.
The idea here is if change is hard, then
just build it into the system so you
have no choice but to constantly change.
And you can also never actually look at
the code. And and I guess I I should
sort of back up and say
the goal here is
to be able to deploy code in production
that was generated by AI of some sort
that humans never reviewed.
Uh and this would have sounded more
crazy 6 months ago. Now a lot of people
are doing this. But at scale and like
big enterprise systems or very complex
older systems, of course, you can't do
this yet, you know.
So
if that is the goal, and why would that
be the goal? Because that's what's going
to happen. We know that's what's going
to happen. Not because like we're
looking at the future and we're looking
at technology trends, but because we
know human behavior and it's way too
easy to do that now. So there people are
always going to do the easy thing. So
let's figure out systems that make the
easy thing okay to do.
Yeah. I think it's also the opportunity.
It's not just that it will happen. It's
also uh uh the the means of staying
competitive is to be able to tap into
that and to take the human out of the
equation. But I, you know, it So as
someone has been saying, you know, code
is going to become disposable a couple
years ago and and, you know, kind of was
dismissed as heresy
not that long ago. Like sort of 2 years
ago. Today doesn't feel as far-fetched.
Uh but let me ask about a few challenges
kind of within within that world. So I
think the the the most blatant one is
uh what is what is sufficient detail in
the spec? And at what point does that
sufficient detail just become a
different piece of code uh that that
you've written? Uh and all you've done
now is like create some sort of template
that's at the top. How would you define
the the right level of specificity
uh in the spec and and which parts
you're happy to delegate to the to the
implementer
uh that is the agent? That's a good
question and the answer changes weekly
kind of, you know. Like I mean, since
you've been talking about this for at
least 2 years, it means probably 4 years
ago you were messing around with code
generation and in the frustration loop
constantly. Like, oh my god, it's magic
and then it's not magic anymore. Fails,
you know.
Uh and I think the last time I felt that
way was like September or October with
the tools available. And now I don't
feel that way anymore. But I know it
doesn't sound like I'm answering the
question, but the reason I'm saying this
is
there's a whole lot more you can
one-shot with very little detail these
days.
Um
however,
uh
like forgetting about the fact that it
just keeps getting smarter and smarter,
I I think the answer for me is that um
I want to iterate until I see the thing
change, right? So uh
like I'm working on
a new IRC network, for example, a reboot
of IRC right now. I didn't one-shot it.
I've got all sorts of interesting
technical things in it. It's called
Freak, by the way. Um
And
when I when I worked on it,
I didn't create a spec that had a great
level of specificity.
But I iterated until I had a spec that
was enough. And I knew it was enough
because I see the evidence in the
software. So it's kind of like you go
back to the early 2000s, we had this
this thing called Naked Objects in Java
where you just like generate Java
objects and it creates the UI for you on
the fly. And the whole idea was a new
Agile way of working with soft with
customers and software where you could
just like pop things open and show that
to them and iterate like that.
Sitting with the customer instead of
like going on these long project things.
Interact with the data model. Yeah.
Yeah, and I think it's the same sort of
thing now where you can iterate and
iterate. The problem this creates though
is
if you want a system that can survive
change over time, you can't just
regenerate the entire thing constantly.
Yeah. So you need to be able to iterate,
but you need to have some way of being
very clear about which things are
changing. So yeah, like there are two
issues. One,
um
if a user knows how to use an
application and it changes every day
because you've re you've changed the
spec and regenerated it and, you know,
re-reimagined an entire UI, that's not
okay. Even if the UI is great, even if
it's better tomorrow than it was today,
users have to actually like understand
how to use the software.
Um
and the other is you just don't want
things that are like core to the
technical foundation of your system to
change constantly because they might be
wrong, right? And that's where this
level of specificity matters a lot where
one intuition, like so an example of
this is I'm building on this IRC
network. So I've got IRC server that
implements the protocol and then I've
got protocol layers on top and another
layer and then I've got clients, you
know, and client SDKs.
At the very bottom level, I want to get
that right quickly and just set it in
stone and probably never change it
unless there's a mistake or we want to
upgrade the IRC protocol, right?
And so the best way to do that would be
if there were some set of specifications
that we iterate on
that we can literally tie through some
like build graph back or to the to the
code that gets generated
and it never has to change unless the
dependency tree changes before it. So we
can change the the protocol all we want
in the beginning and then we sort of
lock it because we never change even the
like vague specs we created that
happened to create a thing that was good
enough. This sounds pretty scary, I
know. And then you just, you know, you
work in the the layer that that makes
sense to do a lot of change. There's a
term, I don't remember the person's name
who coined it, but a term called pace
layers that
sort of uh codifies this idea of
different speeds of change at layers of
a software architecture. Yeah. I think
so so so I've done a fair bit of
thinking of this and in the system
framework that we've since kind of
parked as we focus on Tesla and context
management. And we can get a little bit
into into the delta there.
Uh we we had a lot of uh these elements
and we we talked precisely about that in
that you will create a spec and the spec
can be at whatever level of resolution.
You you reach software that you bless by
using it and looking at it and sort of
deciding that it is good enough. And
then from here you have the question of
stable what you want to achieve is
stable regeneration. Uh so you know, you
you when you regenerate it, you want
stability. Uh you might have a button.
You might not care what color it is and
you're happy to delegate that to the to
the agent, but you don't want to change
in colors every every version. And so
you want some stability over there. Uh
and so you want that and and the the
challenge of course is figuring out what
are the aspects that you want to
um stabilize because uh because
increasingly like those those change.
Like maybe you want the button to be the
same color unless it has a good reason
to change because you've just changed
all of the themes colors and so the
button should also change uh in that
process. And we actually introduced to
use the word lock, you know, we we had
in the system tests for uh for the
different
uh parts of the spec and we you could
lock a test to imply it.
And so so it is very interesting um and
I I I I think probably a bit of an
unsolved and then interesting
interaction model as well of of if you
were to create these different things.
Let's say your information architecture
allowed that.
Uh what is the what is the sort of the
user interaction, you know, that that
you would have with these assets? Um and
maybe I'll I'll I'll throw one more
which is I think there's also an element
of who made the decision that is more
important. If I said something, me the
human in control who is paying the bills
uh and whose neck is on the line,
that should be, you know, more holy than
if the agent has made a decision and
that decision should be more easily
overwritten because it was just making
it at the time. So there's a lot there's
a lot to sort of figure out. I don't
know if you're are you would you
anticipate like new programming this is
like a a frequent question, you know,
that I get as well. It's like would you
anticipate these things
manifesting in in in new programming
language paradigms or in or these just
patterns that will eventually be applied
by the agents? They will manifest in
programming languages, but I think
that's also a step along the way to
where it goes because I
I think what we're going to find is like
any programming language we create is
going to be trying to solve problems
that LLMs can't currently solve with
with plain language
uh and then they'll become obsolete.
Like my first assumption when when I
started doing stuff with chat GPT, you
know, in early early chat GPT days was
oh we should be using like Haskell or
Owl and RSS, you know, like ontologies
and I had all these ideas about static
typing being better and blah blah blah.
It's just all doesn't matter actually.
Um
but I think what what we need instead is
different programming um
paradigms and patterns that aren't
languages.
So, you know, my
my work right now on my implementation
of this Phoenix architecture
is focused on
going from raw human specs to refined um
they're called clauses in my system
where you can like canonicalize actual
intents out and then you can do
hash-based tracking of these intents all
the intents all the way through with
cryptographic hashes
which gives you that build system thing,
but it also gives the ability to add
provenance because I absolutely agree
like capturing intents of the system
uh and capturing who made them uh and
like when and why are really critical
both in
like knowing what to regenerate
and also in just like figuring out how
you would remove things from a system.
That like to me that's the biggest
problem because we're generating things
at such speed, you're going to end up
creating like absolute masses of
garbage. And if the agent did it and not
the person, you know, it's probably okay
to delete. Uh you know, there's a lot of
other
factors you have to check. But like on
my IRC system freak, I actually have two
parallel web apps by accident. I have a
really nice one that I've been iterating
with and then one that the agents just
decided they were going to make and it's
linked some places so I have to remove
it.
Um
but like at least I know in this case
that I made this decision. But I think
what's really interesting is the
combination of what we were just talking
about with specs etc.
and then like capturing the the human
interaction with the LLM as the code is
being built. And there's a bunch of work
going on here of doing this. Um and to
me that's the important thing is like
how do we figure out how to map from
intent all the way through to
uh object of code, whatever that means,
implementation unit in as clear and
replaceable a unit as possible.
Then we have the ability to do this
regenerative software thing for real.
>> Yeah, for real. I think super
interesting and I I guess my my thesis
also would be that there are actually
there are sort of three layers of human
condoning, you know, or like blessing.
There's the explicit instruction that
came from the human developer. There's
the explicit review. I I actually read
this and said yes, which is a bit tricky
because did you really read it? I don't
know, you know, like you technically it
says is this okay? Should I go? And you
said yes. And then there's the you know,
no human interaction. The agents just
decided those. Uh and uh yeah, we had a
lot of those. We by the way referred to
them as shadow specs. Um there's the
spec and the shadow spec
uh which are the decisions you never
made but have been made for you.
Yeah, that's that's a good term. I like
it. And I like I must admit most of the
work that I do I've got mostly shadow
specs with like really high-level stupid
instructions these days and I go YOLO,
you know. So my review my explicit
review I did not read it. I scanned
through it and I'm like yeah, that
sounds right. Exactly. Just replaced it.
Yeah. And there's again there's kind of
these two levels that I don't know how
to sort of name them. There's there's
levels of shadow like, you know, the
shadow and the dark spec, I don't know.
But you know, the ones that you in
theory reviewed and the decisions that
were never presented to you. They were
just made
and you could have proactively gone and
reviewed but you didn't bless.
Like asking about programming languages
reminds me of a conversation I had
earlier this week with a real language
innovator. I won't say who it is cuz I
didn't ask if I could, but
um we were talking about specifically as
I take all these stupid ideas I have and
I try to make them into real code that I
can create projects with. One of the
first things that I ran into was
you know, I keep saying like consistent
calling conventions
uh and ways of dealing with
uh mutations in the system
asynchronously. Is there some sort of
message bus thing? Like there's sort of
these things that happen in my head for
what you need for a Phoenix type
architecture to work.
And the immediate immediate thing that I
run up against when I started generating
this is oh I actually have to choose
like what language and framework. Let's
say I'm going to build a web app. Like
what MVC framework is it going to be in?
What programming language? What runtime?
And I reach the conclusion that
I should just decide this for the entire
system
for any code that's generated.
So like we can start with web apps. I'll
just decide like okay, what's the best
framework for generating it for
generated code for a web app in AI
today?
Uh I think there are two answers to it.
One is whatever the LLM knows, so
probably like two years old old Next.js
or something, you know, React. I I not
things I like. It makes me sort of ill
to say this. Yeah. But it's whatever it
is that has the sort of the the
sweetheart of the weights at the moment.
Exactly. Yeah. Which which tends to sort
of persist historical
uh uh popularity. Yes. Well, now it's
really going to lock in forever because
that's what we're going to keep
regenerating forever.
>> getting duplicated and it feeds itself.
Yeah.
But what really matters now is
uh you know, like I I was all into Ruby
on Rails and evangelism and all this
stuff back in the day, you know, as you
mentioned. I would not do that today. I
would not tie myself to such a thing
because what matters is you have the
code has to be able to be correct. It
has to be as cheap as possible to run.
It has to perform as as well as it can.
It does not have to be human friendly.
It doesn't have to be trendy. It doesn't
even have to have unit tests, [snorts]
you know, you don't have to do peer
review Haskell, you know, the uh
it's okay. So so
what I realized is I'm this Phoenix
architecture
like I don't think
you will decide when you use it
what the like framework is or the
language that it generates. You
shouldn't. That should also be a thing
that's completely open to change.
So, what we'll be compiling to is more
system architectures.
A shape of the system that allows us to
have pluggable, replaceable components
because of the shape of the system
because of the calling conventions and
the consistency and probably some sort
of like type system. There will be these
sort of properties, but they won't be
about the programming language. They'll
be about how this thing runs and how the
components interact. Yeah.
I think um so so that's that's a good
kind of tee up for for a challenge that
I have in my mind. So, uh clearly I've
been on this of the spec-centric
software bandwagon for for a while. Like
literally I've been sort of devoting
kind of my time in in Tessal uh to
pursuing this vision. Uh and uh and like
probably the most significant way in
which I feel like my thinking has has uh
I want to say evolved or at least
changed. You know, maybe it's regressed
uh over time uh is is the move from from
more of
uh thinking about a spec and some some
uh
data format definition in which uh you
properly capture your intent and and the
definition to to wanting to get the
agent to just make good decisions.
Uh and I feel like when you when you
work with humans and like with people on
your team
the the best developers that you have on
the team
uh you or even like you know, yourself
and your future self on it. It's it's
not so much that you expect them to kind
of truly
kind of represent these
uh definitions of your software, right?
Or sort of you know, the historical
decisions that you've made and that need
to blessed and all that. But rather that
you expect them to combine intelligence
and information. You know, it's combine
uh you know, just like smart
decision-making and kind of conclusion
drawing
uh with the right context, you know,
using a term that I think is good for
humans and agents
to to uh put the emphasis in the right
spot. They they should know
how much you care about finance and
budgets versus how much you care about
um uh
you know uh speed and and latency. You
know, how much you care about functional
programming, you know, versus how much
you care about, you know, Ruby. Uh how
much you care about security versus, you
know, like just sort of all of these
different preferences and even your
uh you know, your kind of business
surrounding. So, it's sort of an
understanding of your constraint and
sometimes those constraints may include
it has to be written in this language,
right? Maybe if you are building within
Microsoft and you know, someone condones
it, well, this has to run on Windows.
Right. So, that's a constraint and that
limits some of your options.
Um
So,
I don't know. Like I I really love and
and still expect a
representation of these things to to
manifest, but I wonder where is it that
we even if we're thinking ahead, we're
not thinking sufficiently ahead and we
still like the idea of a data model that
can represent
robustness, right? Or some some
semblance of determinism when really
it's more about making good decisions.
Yeah, I mean I guess like
just um
a random thought from what you were
talking about is I think instead of
specs, we need to be thinking about
building knowledge graphs that
uh yeah, that sounds like a little bit
probably too inflated, but you know,
knowledge graphs of all of these things
whether it be the the values and and and
variance and intents of the the person
that
the beautiful thing with LLMs is they
can actually get they can mine this
stuff from you very easily. They can
say, I feel like you're missing this,
you know, which is sort of how I did it
with with the tests I've been doing with
this Phoenix architecture so far.
Invariants are part of the system and
like metrics of success are part of the
system. And you're right that there's
like a you know,
I don't know, deploy target or build
target or whatever. Like clearly there's
still a Windows app sometimes and
there's still a Mac app sometimes.
Um
the way I'm thinking about it is there's
probably just like a set of patterns
that
uh I'll say I create for myself with
this Phoenix thing, but there's you
know, everyone's going to have their own
uh probably center of gravity of ways of
doing this that they adhere to, but for
mine it would be a set of patterns that
apply to
uh native macOS apps, native iOS apps
for now, web apps, you know, um
TUI apps for consoles or whatever,
server-based things.
Uh and and even, you know, like
distributed systems.
So, then
I have an architecture that I compile
into which can include things like
platform. Um you know, most of the cases
for me I'll be pretty agnostic about
platform and language.
But then you could have different
constraints that you you add to the
system.
Yeah, very hand-wavy wavy abstract stuff
cuz we're we're not there yet, you know.
I mean, the other thing was like we're
talking about apps that manifest, but
maybe there's just a data substrate and
apps
manifest on the fly, you know, it could
be visual or it could be LLMs, whatever
conversation. Yeah, there's probably
still an efficiency element there. So, I
really like it. Like I did also like I
don't want to challenge. I feel
either way we need these data structures
uh for it and and there's, you know, I
think another lesson learned a little
bit is that you can't be too far, you
know, too far out in the future. You
have to think a little bit about it. And
so, I think the Phoenix architecture is
is already fairly dramatically
innovative and a bit of a of a mental
switch to to embrace, you know, for
anybody in the current software
development world. So, even if there is
even if it is a stepping stone, you
know, as you as you think ahead, it is
it is uh very likely to be a kind of
necessary stepping stone. I also really
like how it enables something else that
I think about, which is personalized
software.
Uh and the idea that uh you cuz I I I
find increasingly, I don't know if you
feel the same, which is I use a bunch of
tools that I that I really like.
And I don't I don't really have a
problem with them. I don't want to vibe
code an alternative even if I could.
It's
it's good. It's good. I don't mind
paying them a little bit, you know, it's
what I do. But what I increasingly get
frustrated is that I can't customize
them. Like I want to add They're not
doing They're not have this feature and
I'm annoyed. And it's almost to the
level that's like, you know what? I'm
going to write one of my own just
because I want that feature. And I guess
I'm imagining a world in which
uh you the author can produce a piece of
software that has some of these
definitions of what is what you can muck
about with and what you cannot. You
know, what is the essence of this piece
of software and it has to be embedded.
And what is it that, you know, Chad, if
you want to sort of add a different UI,
a different load out, you know, for
this. Maybe this is one that we do, you
know, we can do cuz APIs and all that.
But you can modify it.
Um and like have you thought about like
the Phoenix
the Phoenix architecture or or whatever
the I don't know how to kind of call the
the whole thing, but like that type of
platform being an actual distributable
that this is the software that you're
sending off to you to users?
Yeah, I think so. Although my
uh it's not that I disagree, but the way
I've been thinking about this is more
from the data model up. Um and it comes
from like the local-first community. Uh
specifically
um well, I think Ink and Switch wrote a
a good thing called malleable software
about some of this. Um
but you know, like in the local-first
community, it's all about your data is
local. It's on your device. People write
applications that interact with that
data. And then they, you know, you have
CRDTs etc. for for synchronizing this
stuff.
Um
so
why wouldn't you have like a shared data
model across uh and I'm sort of not
answering a question you didn't ask, but
imagine you had a shared data model of
all the sort of common things you need
to do. And anyone could write software
that allows you to interact with your
shared data models. So, it could be your
productivity stuff like meetings and
tasks and emails and stuff.
Um
if it's not in a cloud and it's not on
some private server that you have to
deploy to, but rather it's a software
that you run locally, then manifesting
new interfaces to these things is sort
of just like an assumption.
Because third parties, you know, maybe
one one company writes software that you
start using. Let's say Linear, which is
actually local-first software.
Um someone else could then come along
very easily and write the second
interface to that same stuff and Linear
can't stop you. They wouldn't want to.
You know, that's part of the point of
doing local-first software. And maybe
I'm just like an old uh
stupid software developer that's, you
know, still chasing this idea of
reusability and and the semantic web and
everything. But you know, what if we
could now think industry-wide or at
least in pockets of consortia about like
doing local-first as as a default
and having shared data models um
by default. You know, schemas, JSON
schema, whatever it is.
Uh schema.org that is.
So, then
new vibe coded apps just talk to this
stuff and there's an assumption that
it's there. I think this is really
interesting. Um
the the the other idea of like
constraining which parts are are
malleable
is
interesting. Although I don't see why
there should be a limit to which pieces
of the software you should be able to
change.
Uh
though maybe
you know, from an IT department
perspective, I I do see it cuz, you
know, someone calls and says my software
doesn't work cuz I changed it, that's a
bad thing.
But part of it is not so much the
constraint about what you're allowed and
not allowed to change. Like at least a
portion of it is is just, you know, like
if you if you who in Wunderlist and you
created and you've spent this deep
thinking about, you know, choosing the
right functionality or visuals or like
means of it or the things that will
drive the correct kind of to-do list
handling and so I I don't want to lose
that. I just want to add this feature.
So it's more like de-risk me when I add
my sort of experts to my own social
network button that didn't exist on it
because, you know, I wanted to extend
it. Can you Can you help me preserve,
you know, Chad's brain, you know, when
you when you when I got the software
from you and just modified I mean, like
big software does this, right? Like CRMs
and all those you would customize your
organization. I just find it interesting
to think about uh Yeah, it is a great
idea because, you know, one of the
things that we all when you start
talking about regenerative software, the
immediate like uh pushback is you can't
just regenerate the whole thing. The
users won't know how to use it. So it's
true that if you could like define even
pace layers within the UI maybe like
this panel and this panel or these types
of panels are things that are always
extensible. It makes sense and you're
right. It's like a lesson from the '90s
or '80s, right? You know, like
uh this has been a thing in enterprise
software forever. It usually not because
they want to preserve the experience
because the experience is usually not
very good, but everyone needs to
customize them. Yeah.
Yeah, to differentiate. And I and I I
love the idea of pace layers and and to
be to be clear, I am a huge fan of
reusability. I think even if you get to
the point in which LLMs can create and
agents can create everything from
scratch with a very high
uh reliability, that is so massively
inefficient, right? I want to create a
to-do app and it needs to build a
kernel. I I mean, why why would it do
that? And, you know, familiarity between
different systems, consistency within
enterprise systems, just mutual
learnings, right? When there's a bug, I
don't want that everybody to kind of
shave and, you know, have all of these
problems. So Yeah, but the the
efficiency thing is a a really
interesting one. I was talking a couple
weeks ago with um
one of the founders of Radical, which is
this open open distributed GitHub sort
of replacement. Um
he is now working on something called
Radiant Computer.
And it's like a ground-up operating
system that he's building.
And he's thinking obviously a lot about
LLMs and and he wrote a piece uh about
how you can sort of like
reduce the surface area of how you
interact with something, let's say an
operating system
uh to the benefit of efficiency of LLM
use. It's part of what he's doing is
like everything is private by default
and you can run local models, etc. Of
course, you're dealing with like local
power constraints and the fact that the
models aren't quite as good as the
frontier models.
And it's it's an obvious
thing to reach, but somehow there's this
beauty in in the the insight that
if you like you start with an open
playing field and then you create this
constrained language that actually
expresses what the system's supposed to
do. And I think this is like a version
of what you're talking about. Then it
becomes a very easy thing for the LLMs
to interact with it. And you can do this
over time with every system where it
starts with this open field and then it
becomes, you know, it congeals. Maybe
this is like what programming languages
are in the future. You asked our, you
know, about new programming languages. I
don't know if there's another guy uh Guy
Steele
um who is a you I'm sure you know of
him. He's a well-known programming
language researcher.
He did an amazing talk at OOPSLA in like
'98, I think, called Growing a Language
that
I like every generation I I reintroduce
it to people because it's always
relevant somehow. But the talk starts
with him
uh defining a subset of English from
scratch that he can use for the talk.
And it's all this big lesson on building
up vocabulary and building up
foundations you can then be expressive.
Uh and maybe that's what what we end up
evolving toward because in this agent
this like rapid change rapid uh software
creation environment we should be able
to create tons of reusable vocabulary
like this. It should and we should be
able to easily differentiate between
what's reusable for me, what's reusable
for my organization, and what's reusable
for the world. And the ideal state is
that we
like figure out markets for this or ways
of sharing this stuff. Yeah, no,
absolutely. And we we've gone through
all of that type of thinking as well at
uh at Tessell in the early days. It's
like he create a an HTML to markdown
converter for me. Sounds like a simple
spec. Which HTML do you mean?
Uh which which markdown do you mean? Uh
on it? You know, to be loaded in a
browser. Which browser?
So and and and and um and and these
things rot over time, right? Like
whatever, you know, if you interpret it
today's, you know, LLMs will interpret
the thing from 2 years ago. Well, I
guess actually maybe it stays the same
cuz it's persisting itself, but in over
time the definition, you know, in 5
years now.
Hey everyone. Hope you're enjoying the
episode so far. [music]
Our team is working really hard behind
the scenes to bring you the best guests
so we can have the most informative
conversations about agentic development.
Whether that's talking about the latest
tools, the most efficient workflows, or
defining best practices. But for
whatever reason, many of you have yet to
subscribe to the channel. If you're
enjoying the podcast and want us to
continue to bring you the very best
content, please do us a favor and hit
that subscribe button. It really [music]
does make a difference and lets us
continue to improve the quality of our
guests and build an even [music] better
product for you.
All right, back to the episode. So I
want to I want to ask you though about
another set of posts that you have
there. There's more about uh evaluations
and durability. And so if if if
everything is regenerated and as we sort
of we've been talking here, there's some
not that that's not always ideal and
there's some
accumulation of learnings and
preferences and and distributions.
Um you know, you have a statement that
said evaluations are the real code base,
you know, they are
uh in one of these posts. I guess how do
you think about durability? What is it
that as I build IP or as I build, you
know, build up anything
um
persists across
Yeah, so I I do say this thing about
evaluations and it might be an
overloaded word where it sounds like I'm
talking about some like modern uh
definition of evaluations in the context
of LLMs or ML and I'm not uh although I
also am. I'm really talking about
invariants, metrics, constraints, all
these things that that we were just
talking about, you know, um
like to take a stupid just because it'll
be easy to talk about. Let's say you
have uh I don't know an order record in
a database and and you're just talking
about like the CRUD operations for
orders in a in a e-commerce system.
Um you know, there would be like
[clears throat] correctness requirements
obviously. There might be side effects
that you expect when an order is placed
that should also happen so that you can
like measure the fact that that happens.
There might be speed constraints. There
might be memory constraints or IO or you
know, all these sort of like system
level things.
Uh
and and to me like this set of stuff and
this is kind of why I was talking about
knowledge graph earlier versus specs cuz
I think you have to create this
knowledge graph which may be pretty
pretty inscrutable that we probably need
tools for dealing with this, too.
But it captures all this intent that's
both business intent and and technical
intent.
Now, in my old naive way of doing things
>> [snorts]
>> which is still the way I would do it for
now.
Um
like I would always talk to my teams
about uh focusing on mean time to
resolution of problems versus mean time
between failure.
Which was another way of saying like
don't worry so much about testing
everything up front, but let's just make
sure everything is really well
instrumented so that we and we can
easily roll back. And so like my way of
changing software is YOLO in production.
Yeah, you know, just to sort of
overstate the point. Yeah. And then
immediately respond to the live metrics
and the you know, the real state of the
system via intense observability at all
layers including business and and
technical.
I think there's probably some aspect of
of that still Right. at least for now uh
in a system that's going to be changing
rapidly like this.
Um the other thing is you can create
tests
uh and you can do it both before and
after the fact. You can do it really
rapidly with with AI now. So I think
there's a thing where
uh and you were talking about like
locked tests, I think, in in your way of
thinking. Because if you test otherwise,
you don't know what to what to trust,
right? You you you take some spec, you
create code, you create tests, they
disagree. Who's right? Exactly. Yeah.
My way of thinking about it right now is
there's a there's like at least a layer
of tests that like everything is locked.
There isn't differentiation between
locked and not locked. Of course, I'm
not writing tests anymore.
I'm not writing any of the code, but,
you know, so I'm explicitly talking to
the agents about the purpose of the
tests. And the purpose of the tests is
based on our current under understanding
of the system like in my IRC system, for
example.
I I will go through runs where I have it
just like look for all of the possible
edge cases we might not have thought of
for a certain class of bugs. And I get
multiple models multiple times to do
this.
And then I review it and I have it
create tests that discover bugs.
And then I have it work until the tests
run all the time and I keep this layer
locked all the time. So that's sort of
like the second way I'm thinking about
um evaluations now.
I I think probably it goes further and
further when
we can collectively spend more time on
specs to canonicalized requirements to
invariants and this sort of chain
because that gives you something
different to reason about in a more
automated way. But right now I think
just this sort of
metrics plus tests is the way to go. I'm
a big believer in evaluations. I think
in the um
like first year, if you will, of
Tessell, I was thinking a lot about
tests as the things that persist. And
you'll have tests, you will lock tests.
This is the behavior of the
functionality. Increasingly, in in my
current worldview, I I think more about
making good decisions. And and so the
tests that I want are more the tests of
my agent's behavior as opposed to the
tests of the system that has been built.
Uh and those are
class I don't know if you'd call
anything classic these days, right? But
those are AI evaluations of saying,
"Hey, is the agent behaving as I am?"
And I guess I I perceive that to be a
higher leverage point because you are
you're making the developer that you
want versus making the system that you
want. And the developer that you want is
actually much more powerful than a
system
because they can create the system that
you want at a at a fairly high fidelity.
Um and what's interesting is that the
same concept that you said right now is
true, though. Like there's still a a
little bit of you have to capture and
aggregate what are the evaluations that
are that represent what you want. And
you probably have to accumulate them.
Uh and over time you need to curate
them, which is still like a you know, we
don't know how to we don't know how to
deal with that yet, you know, we have to
think But but at least evaluations speak
in slightly higher level terms of like
when when this happens, that happens,
you know, like the behavior uh the the
developer behaves like this. It's still
a volume challenge
of of those do you do you assess? Um but
then once you build once you get that,
the instructions, the specs actually are
malleable
uh themselves because they are
um
they also change with the models, right?
Like the way that you would instruct
Haiku is different since that
effectively is different than the way
you would instruct Opus. Um and we see
already that, you know, Opus is very
creative, but it's a bit of a smart ass
and it doesn't follow instructions. And
you know, Codex is less creative, but it
is more obedient, you know, in that
sense. And you know, Gemini has its own
strengths. And just each of these things
is different.
Uh and so when you when you think about
these like again, if you really continue
down the same rabbit hole
and you continue you you you move from
programming languages to program
programmer language, right? It's the
language with which you instruct the
agent versus the language with which you
define the system. That's really an
interesting approach. And and I I feel
this like I switched from Opus to
another model
trying to arbitrage credits
uh
a week ago. And I had a very frustrating
day until I woke up the next morning and
realized, "Oh, I changed the model.
That's why it feels like, you know, 2025
again."
Uh I blamed the model. I probably should
blame myself in the way I interact with
the model. However, um
uh that actually sort of makes a point.
Like when you said try and make the best
programmer, I think this is a really
cool approach. And it's absolutely the
opposite of the way I think about it.
I just assume the programmers are both
idiots now
and going to be geniuses later. And
they're going to progress at different
paces depending on the model. And so I'm
I lean toward trying to create a system
of code generation. And maybe that's the
programmer. I don't know, but it's not
an intelligence, you know, but a system
that allows me to plug in the most
idiotic LLM here and the genius here and
still have some results that I feel I
can I can trust. But also decouples me
from thinking about the models
underneath.
They're just going to keep changing and
getting better. Of course, eventually
all this stuff that we're talking about
is going to be irrelevant, too, and
obsolete cuz the models are just There's
a different point in the future, which
is
you know, having kind of a a more
intelligent conversation by a couple of
AI models than what we're sort of having
here. But yeah, and I think for this
work, I think you need both because I
think amidst the team, you need some
form of definition of the outputs of
that, you know, intelligent programmer
that that captures the definition of
your system and makes it easier for the
programmer to be, you know, less
intelligent or even even just to capture
the alignment on what the system does.
And you know, making that increasingly
LLM friendly so it's easy for them to
understand and kind of apply and
represent instructions. And then you
separately need the instructions of the
of the developer. And I I I think to me,
context engineering is about that,
right? And I think we started writing
and we'll probably talk more about the
context development life cycle. And I
think I think the agents will handle the
software development life cycle. And we
need developers to sit in the context
development life cycle as we develop
context. And the context really is the
operator's manual, right? It is about
how do how should the agents behave
and what your intent is. It'll be
interesting to see the interplay there.
Yeah, a friend of mine, Jess Martin, is
working on something called context
library, which is a way of automating
building up context of all of these
these decisions that you make. Yeah.
With the goal being kind of like what
you're saying, run agents all night
while you're asleep and they make
decisions based on probably what you
would have said because they have enough
context in the system built up.
>> The way that's usable by them.
I see a lot of that. And then I I do
wonder the reason I say context
development and I think it's a different
view on it, although I time will tell
which one is right,
which is there's this spontaneous
spontaneous, you know, observe me and
understand what I do. But then what I do
today is not the same as I would have
done a year ago. And let alone 10 years
ago. And so like the the ultimate
approach is context is a thing you
develop. It is not a point in time. And
we all know like at one point during the
LLM kind of iterations, all the rage was
learn my code base. And then we learned
like
there's a bunch of stuff in my code base
that I do not want replicated. In fact,
most of the stuff in my code base I do
not want replicated cuz it's been
accumulating garbage. And garbage in,
garbage out.
Uh and and so it's not that it's not
useful, but you want to develop your
sort of practice. So it's interesting.
I guess
uh maybe it's a good point to sort of
try and conclude the conversation in the
point of timeline.
So what is your thesis? Like you're
building put aside sort of the the guide
to the programmer even side, the switch
from
current day software to immutable
regenerative, you know, Phoenix
architecture style software.
Like what what do you think is a is a
practical or what is your anticipation
in terms of the
uh the the path of adoption for software
actually changing to be working like
this in the industry? I I think it will
be both really quick and incredibly
slow. And the the slow part is the
realization we need to all make that we
have systems that have been in
development for decades and no one
understands them.
And most of us nerds out on the frontier
are not thinking about them so much yet.
I think some of us start are starting
to.
Um so like
uh I think, you know, if I were to go
start a company now,
I would be doing the company this way
today. So, you know, greenfield code
base right now. Now is the answer. And I
know some people who are doing this to,
you know, varying degrees.
Uh
but
I also know of development shops in, you
know, fairly forward-leaning companies
that are barely touching AI at all. And
they're resistant. And there's a huge
portion of the developer population
that's afraid or just not paying
attention. Yeah, just like when Java
happened, they didn't want to do Java.
They didn't want to do Ruby and Python,
you know. Uh and uh you know, they just
want to have fun and and go to work as
as little as they can. That is the truth
about most people in their jobs, which
is fine. That's, you know, humans are
humans.
Um but organizations are backward.
Organizations are slow. Most people
don't know how to deal with this and
they're going to be looking at like
large consulting companies to try and
figure it out. So, I think it's
a long, long time before
there's a mass adoption of AI-generated
software up and down the stack through,
you know, the largest enterprises.
Um but there's going to there's a lot of
interesting work that should be
happening probably in the coming year or
two
because so many of us in companies I'm
talking to, you know, from my
perspective as a VC
are
having these same conversations about
like trying to capture intent. And what
is a spec versus intent? And where can
intent come from? You could mine it from
corporate email systems for, you know,
the last several decades. You've got all
that stuff captured. You could mine it
from source control system, project
management.
So, work being done to figure out the
legacy intent of its legacy systems so
that you can then start automating maybe
like strangler fig pattern breaking
pieces of an application off.
Um
but yeah, I think it's going to be like
insanely fast on one side and
surprisingly slow on the other side.
>> Yeah. I think that's a good
it's almost always like the right answer
into like any diffusion of technology. I
do what one of the things that I do feel
and maybe this is in sort of Tessell on
the company building ethos side is that
one of the reasons that we've kind of
focused on on the sort of, you know,
train train the developer versus, you
know, define the system in in the
offering, you know, there's there's a
whole bunch of reasons some of this
stuff needs to, you know, be open
source, needs to sort of be part of the
agents, you know, there's a variety of
reasons. But part of it is that if you
train the programmer,
then you're sort of simulating the human
behaviors, right? Like in these ancient
systems that are so fragile, there are
still humans, they're operating in there
and they're making decisions.
Uh and those decisions are, you know, by
and large these companies are still
alive, right? Like they are they are
growing, they're modifying it. And so
there's some logic by which they are
making this work. And so we felt like
it's
even though conceptually as we talk
about the it's a higher layer and it's
maybe a further future to think about
training the programmer versus training
the
there's actually in some aspects of it
a more
short-term applicability of it because
that better programmer can help you do
better on the systems even if it doesn't
fix the fragility or it doesn't make
those systems you know be able to rise
up from the ashes.
Yeah, I agree. I mean I think you know,
it's like what I said about everything's
going to be obsolete that we're talking
about at some point. I think there are
waves where we will solve these problems
in the way we're talking about today and
it's totally valid and it will be useful
for a long time.
But the industry is just going to go so
fast we'll think oh God, what we're
talking about now is silly, but it's
still useful. But it's maybe not the
future anymore, you know, the beautiful
thing about today is we can go so fast.
We can deal with all these different
phases. You know, and we can have road
maps for our companies that
where we just say okay, we'll get to
that when it's a problem. Okay, now it's
a problem. Boom. Next week we got a
whole new release, you know. It's like a
miraculous time to be a software
developer as well as a terrifying one.
But yeah, I think it's it's where we get
to be like
steering [snorts] through this crazy
time. It's really exciting. Yeah, yeah,
definitely sort of fasten your seat
belts, but
it is it is an exhilarating ride.
Chad, this has been super super fun, you
know,
fascinating, future-looking, you know,
sort of deep on it and and I think right
in many ways. So I'm really looking
forward to to the open source version of
it and to hear more about
about this development.
I don't know if you want to say if like
if people are are keen to to find you to
invest in their sort of you know,
invention of sort of future of software
development, where can they find you?
Probably Blue Sky is the best place. I'm
Chad Fowler.com on Blue Sky. Sounds
good.
So thanks again for coming on to the
show. Thank you. Very fun.
>> Thanks everyone for tuning in and I hope
you join us for the next one.